Viewers, what do you think can make us be talking all the time about our situation
instead of the Redeemer?
Our sin.
Right now viewers, be free from the power of sin!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I release you from the power of evil thoughts, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
It is sin that can make one to be talking and thinking about challenges
instead of talking about the Redeemer, Jesus Christ.
You are released from the power of sin!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be free from anything that means pain, anything that means trouble,
anything that means sickness and disease!
Anything that means career failure - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You know what Jesus can do - beyond your dreams!
Anything that means setback - be free, in the name of Jesus!
Be free, in the name of Jesus!
You were with Joseph in adverse circumstances and helped him.
Help Your children, in the name of Jesus!
In whatever circumstances - help Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Be it poverty, hardship, sickness or disease, career failure -
help Your children, in the name of Jesus!
As You did Joseph - help Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Help Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing on you! Hear the Healer - be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
I command deliverance on you!
Hear the Deliverer -
be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Freedom, breakthrough!
I can hear freedom, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear breakthrough, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to Him for giving you faith to believe.
Viewers all over the world, I rejoice with you!
I rejoice with you!
I rejoice with you, in Jesus Christ's name!
Hallelujah!
Give thanks to Him from your heart.
From your heart, give thanks to God.